{"data":[{"question":"I was____hospital in March.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"1","explain":" Prepositions of Place: at, in, on\n- At for a point: at the corner, at the bus stop, at the door, at the top of the page, at the front desk...\n- In for an enclosed space: in the garden, in London, in a box, in my wallet, in a industry...\n- On for a surface: on the wall, on the floor, on a page...","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"39","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"2"},{"question":"There were a lot of people _____ the party.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"2","explain":"- On your side: I support\/ agree with you","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"39","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"2"},{"question":"Mr Smith's office is_____ the second floor.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"3","explain":"- In: doing or affecting a particular kind of job (in study, in education, in industry)","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"39","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"2"},{"question":"Ernest works ____ an office","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"1","explain":"- Prepositions of time: at, in, on:\n+  in: for months, years, centuries, long periods\n+ at: for a precise time (at 3 o'clock, at noon, at sunrise, at the moment)\n+ on: for days and dates (on sunday, on 6 March, on Christmas Day, on my birthday...)","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"39","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"2"},{"question":"Michael was born _____ 1962.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"1","explain":"- On: used to say what part of someone's body is touching the ground or another surface and supporting their weight","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"39","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"2"},{"question":"Have you ever ridden _____ a donkey?","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"3","explain":"- In: used to name the book, document, film etc where something or someone appears","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"39","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"2"},{"question":"Please put more potatoes _____ my plate.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"3","explain":"- Prepositions of Place: at, in, on\n- At for a point: at the corner, at the bus stop, at the door, at the top of the page, at the front desk...\n- In for an enclosed space: in the garden, in London, in a box, in my wallet, in a industry...\n- On for a surface: on the wall, on the floor, on a page...","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"39","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"2"},{"question":"More people are retiring _____ 62 instead of the traditional 65.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"2","explain":"Prepositions of Place: at, in, on\n- At for a point: at the corner, at the bus stop, at the door, at the top of the page, at the front desk...\n- In for an enclosed space: in the garden, in London, in a box, in my wallet, in a industry...\n- On for a surface: on the wall, on the floor, on a page...","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"39","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"2"},{"question":"Mrs. Smith was notified_____ a Wednesday afternoon last March.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"3","explain":"Prepositions of Place: at, in, on\n- At for a point: at the corner, at the bus stop, at the door, at the top of the page, at the front desk...\n- In for an enclosed space: in the garden, in London, in a box, in my wallet, in a industry...\n- On for a surface: on the wall, on the floor, on a page...","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"39","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"2"},{"question":"There were more than 10,000 people _____ the concert last night.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"2","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"39","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"2"}]}